# **Devang Patel**

Senior Product Designer

#### Info

Phone

+49 152 5235 0106

**Email** 

pateldevang10@gmail.com

### Links

Personal Website

LinkedIn

Dribbble

#### Skills

Visual Design

User Interface design

User Experience Design

Interaction Design

Visual Systems Design

Rapid Prototyping

Qualitative research

Data Visualization

HTML, CSS, Javascript,

React, React Native

Wordpress

# Languages

Gujarati

Hindi

English

German (A1)

## **Profile**

Multidisciplinary designer with over 10 years of experience specializing in visual design, interaction design, and front-end technologies. My design skills and strong technical knowledge allows me to take any idea from concept to functional digital product.

# **Employment History**

#### Senior Product Designer, Omio

Mar 2018 − Present Perlin

- Designed product features for Omio's ferries experience.
- Leading company's design language system that's being used by designers & engineers.
- As a part of Omio's re-branding team, I helped redesign the core experience of web & apps, also built a design system in parallel to keep things consistent while scaling up.
- Built an internal website for design system to make it easily accessible & adaptable.
- Worked with designers & front-end engineers to setup contribution guidelines and processes for the system.

#### Lead Designer, Mokko, LLC

Mar 2016 − Dec 2017 Physical Ahmedabad

- Lead design for local food delivery startup 'Tiffinity', Designed everything from branding to cross platform apps.
- Designed & built react UI components library called 'Substance UI' and published it as npm package with help of engineers.
- Built simple news-reading app for iOS & Android called 'NewsDeck'

#### UI/UX Designer, Freelancer

Oct 2014 − Dec 2017 PAhmedabad

#### Creative Designer, IndiaNIC Infotech Ltd

#### Web Designer, Freelance

Jan 2013 − Jan 2014 PAhmedabad

#### Web Designer & Front End Developer, iCreators Technology

### Web & Graphic Designer, Advanced Hair Studio India

#### Web Designer, iCreators

Jul 2010 − Jan 2011 PAhmedabad

# Education

Som-Lalit College of Commerce, Gujarat University, Bachelor of Commerce 2009 − 2011 

Ahmedabad

PCE - Perfect Computer Education, Diploma in Web Technology

Dec 2009 − May 2010 P Ahmedabad